thesecret.tv 2019-07-11

# Privacy Policy | The Secret - Official Website

**The Secret Customer Privacy Policy**

The Secret’s Customer Privacy Policy covers the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that may be collected by Prime Time US Inc. (“The Secret” or “us” or “we”) anytime you interact with The Secret, visit our website or use our app. Please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information. Your privacy is a priority at The Secret, and we go to great lengths to protect it.

The Secret reserves the right to update this privacy policy from time to time.

**Why We Collect Personal Information**

We collect your personal information because it helps us deliver a superior experience and level of customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products and services and focus on categories of greatest interest to you. In addition, your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product and other announcements, special offers, and events that you might like to hear about.

**What Information We Collect and How We May Use It**

We will ask for your personal information if you wish to contact us using the “Contact” form, sign up for our weekly scrolls, submit your story online, subscribe to our newsletter or other mailings, or otherwise communicate with us. We may at that time require that you provide personal information, including without limitation your name, address, phone number and email address.

If you choose to connect with The Secret through a third-party social network such as Facebook, Instagram, Twitter, or others, we may collect personal information you provide in your profile on such third-party social networks, including without limitation your name, username, e-mail address, photograph, gender and date of birth.  
We may also collect certain non-personally identifiable information regarding customer activities on our website. This helps us to determine how best to provide useful information to customers and to understand which parts of our websites, products, and Internet services are of most interest to them.

If you partake in any contests, sweepstakes or games via the website or app, you may be required to undertake a separate registration process requiring the submission of personal information such as your name, street address, city, state and zip code, email address, telephone number and date of birth. The applicable entry page and/or rules will provide the specific requirements.

We may use your personal information to provide services that you have requested, respond to your requests, and send you communications, as well as for auditing, research, and analysis to improve the products offered on our website and app. You always will be given the opportunity to unsubscribe from further emails in any promotional messages we send you.

Please note that if you choose to purchase our products online via our website, you will be transferred to one of our e-commerce partners, which will accept your order and process your payment. The Secret does not collect or store any payment information, or process any orders. Each of our e-commerce partners, such as Amazon, Barnes & Noble, iTunes, Google Play, and others, has its own privacy policy, which will apply to all online orders. You should read and familiarize yourself with the applicable partner’s Privacy Policy and other applicable terms.

**Publicly Displayed Information is Public**

If you use a story submission feature or bulletin board or chat room on The Secret website or app, you should be aware that any information you share may be visible to other users. Personally identifiable information you submit in this manner can be read, collected, or used by other individuals to send you unsolicited messages. The Secret is not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in this manner. For example, if you submit a story that includes information that was previously non-public, The Secret will collect that information from your interaction and the information may become publicly available.  
When We Disclose Your Information The Secret takes your privacy very seriously. The Secret does not sell or rent your contact information to other marketers.

To help us provide superior service, your personal information may be shared with the holder of the copyrights to the website and to the products sold on it, including The Secret book and film, who will take steps to safeguard it in accordance with our privacy policy.

There are also times when The Secret makes certain personal information about you available to companies or individuals to provide products and services to you on our behalf. These companies may help us process information, extend credit, fulfill customer orders, deliver products to you, manage and enhance customer data, provide customer service, assess your interest in our products and services, or conduct customer research or satisfaction surveys. We call them our “Service Providers.” We may share personally identifiable information with Service Providers solely as appropriate for them to perform their functions, but they may not use such information for any other purpose, except if we inform you otherwise at the time of collection. Without such information being made available, it would be difficult for you to purchase products, have products delivered to you, receive customer service, provide us feedback to improve our products and services, or access certain services, offers, and content on the website.

At times we may be required by law or litigation to disclose your personal information. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance, disclosure is necessary.

**How We Protect Your Personal Information**

The Secret takes precautions – including administrative, technical, and physical measures – to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. We use reasonable and customary measures to safeguard the security of your personal information; however transmissions made on or through the Internet are vulnerable to attack and cannot be guaranteed to be secure. You hereby acknowledge that we are not responsible for any intercepted information sent via the Internet, and you hereby release us from any and all claims arising out of or related to the use of intercepted information in any unauthorized manner.

**Cookies, Tracking and Other Technologies**

Like many websites, The Secret’s website uses “cookies” and other technologies to help us understand which parts of our websites are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how much time they spend there. We may use cookies and other technologies to study traffic patterns on our website. This information helps us make the website even more rewarding and helps us study the effectiveness of our customer communications. We also use cookies to customize your experience and provide greater convenience each time you interact with us. For example, your contact information and information about your computer helps us provide you with customer service. You may have the ability to decline to permit cookies or other tracking technology, but in that case we cannot promise you that all features of the website will function properly as a result.

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. The Secret will not use this type of collected information to market directly to that person.

In some of the email messages from us or those whose products are available on our website, we use a “click-through URL” linked to content on The Secret website. When customers click one of these URLs, they pass through our web server before arriving at the destination web page. We may track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked, simply avoid clicking text or graphic links in the email.

California Do Not Track Disclosures: because we respect your privacy, we will abide by any “do not track” technology that you may choose to utilize, although, as described above with cookies, such technology may negatively affect the functionality of the website.

**Third-Party Sites**

The Secret’s website has links to the sites of third parties. The Secret is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies.

Children and Minors

Our website and app are intended for use by adults only and we do not knowingly collect or use any personal information from minors under the age of 13. If we collect personal information from someone we learn to be under 13 years of age, such personal information shall immediately be deleted. If you are a parent or guardian of a child under 13 years of age and you believe your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us at privacy@thesecret.tv.

If you are a California resident under the age of 18, and a registered user of our website, California Business and Professions Code Section 22581 permits you to request and obtain removal of content or information you have publicly posted. To make such a request, please send an email with a detailed description of the specific content or information to privacy@thesecret.tv and include “CA Removal Request” in the subject line. Please be aware that such a request does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information you have posted and that there may be circumstances in which the law does not require or allow removal even if requested.

**Changes**

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. In the event we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, such policy will be re-posted in on our website and in the app with the date such modifications were made indicated on the top of the page. Therefore, please review this Privacy Policy from time to time so that you are aware when any changes are made to this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions about the changes that were implemented, please contact us at privacy@thesecret.tv and include “Information Regarding Updated Policy” in the subject line. In any event, your continued use of the website and/or app after such change constitutes your acceptance of any such change(s), and if you do not accept any changes, you may choose not to use our website or app, or opt out by sending us an appropriate notice.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

Under certain circumstances, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 states that, upon receipt of a request by a California customer, a business may be required to provide detailed information regarding how that business has shared that customer’s personal information with third parties for direct marking purposes. However, the foregoing does not apply to businesses like ours that do not disclose personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes without prior approval. California users may request further information about their rights under this law and our policy by writing to us at privacy@thesecret.tv, using the subject line “CA Request for Information,” and requesting further information.

**_Special Notice to Residents of the European Economic Area_**

Residents of the European Economic Area (“EEA”), including the European Union (“EU”) who have consented to provide personal data to subscribe to The Secret Scrolls Email List are subject to the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) effective May 25, 2018.   Your use of and subscription to The Secret Scrolls Email List is entirely optional and you may always unsubscribe by following the link included on every e-mail communication.   By subscribing to the list, you consent to having your personal data, including your e-mail address, stored and processed in the United States, which has different privacy laws than the EU.

If you have any questions regarding the personal data that we collect or retain, including requests that we change or update your personal data, requests for copies of your personal data, or requests that we delete your personal data or if you wish to unsubscribe from The Secret Scrolls Email List, please contact us at [privacy@thesecret.tv](mailto:privacy@thesecret.tv).  We use AWeber to process the personal data of EU residents for the Secret Scrolls Email List and AWeber acts as the processor for such information.  We also abide by AWeber’s Privacy Policy and Customer Terms of Service which may be accessed at <https://www.aweber.com/privacy.htm> and <https://www.aweber.com/service-agreement.htm>.

**Legal Disclaimer**

Our website and app operate AS-IS, and we do not represent or warrant that they will be available at all times, or that your use of the website and/or app will be uninterrupted or error-free. We are not responsible for your ability to access the website or app, or for matters beyond our control. This Privacy Policy is governed by California law, excluding its provisions on choice of law.

**Privacy Questions**

If you have questions or concerns about The Secret’s Website Privacy Policy or data processing, please contact us at privacy@thesecret.tv. The Secret Data Controller in your region will respond to your inquiry within 30 days.

Last revised May 25th, 2018
